Okay, so let's look at a register naming
quiz solution. So we have seen the first
instruction renamed. Let's now rename
the second one. It's going to be an ad.
R1 and R2 are going to be P1 and P7. R1
is where we put the result. Remember,
you don't use this. You rename it to the
next physical register. So we have P8.
Then we have the multiplication of R4
and R4. This is P4 P4. You write the new
value of R2 and that means that this P7
now becomes P9. Then we have the add of
R3 and R2 which are P3 and P9 right as a
result to R3 which becomes P10 before
that happens. And then this
multiplication will read R six and R
six. That's our P6 and P6 here. produce
a result and put it in R2. So now R2
gets to become P1. And finally we have
this ad of R5 and R2. This is P5 and P1.
Produce a result and put it in R5. So R5
now instead of P5 becomes P12. And
that's the solution to the quiz.